

Curriculum Vitae

PERSONAL

Name: Rumil Christian T. Seloveres

Address: Purok-1 Estaca, Pilar, Bohol Zipcode: 6321

Phone number: 09661552780 (Globe)/ 09923777336 (Dito)

Email: rumil.christian@gmail.com

Date of birth: 24-10-2000

Place of birth: Tagbilaran City

Gender: Male

Nationality: Filipino

Marital status: Single

RESUME OBJECTIVE

I'm Rumil Christian T. Seloveres, 23 years of age studying at the University of Bohol with the course of Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering. I'm eager to learn and to enhance my competence and gain relevant and practical industrial skills pertaining to my course taken. I can create a software program using Java programming language, creating 3D designs using AutoCAD, basic c, c++, c# programming and I assure you that I'm the person you want in your company based on my skillset.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2017 – May 2017 Sales Clerk

Alturas Group of Companies, Tagbilaran City

A sales clerk in the Alturas Mall.

Dec 2018 – Jan 2019 Work Immersion

LGU - Pilar, Municipality of Pilar, Pilar, Bohol

Encoder and Assistant Computer Technician

June 2019 – April 2020 Student Assistant/Working Scholar

University of Bohol, Tagbilaran City

Assistant Encoder, Cleaner

02/13/2024 - 03/27/2024 On-The-Job Training Program

IT Internship Program - Pedicab Solutions Inc.,

Tagbilaran City

Web Developer Intern

EDUCATION

2012 - 2013 Grade 1 - Grade 6

Estaca Elementary School, Estaca, Pilar, Bohol

2013 - 2017 Grade 7 - Grade 10 High School

Pilar Technical-Vocational High School, Poblacion Pilar

2017 - 2019 Grade 11 - Grade 12 Senior High School

Pilar Technical-Vocational High School, Poblacion Pilar

2019 – 2024 (Present) Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

(BSCOMPE)

University of Bohol, Tagbilaran City

REFERENCES

Engr. Liduvina Namocatcat Instructor

Email: llnamocatcat@gmail.com, Cell: +63 (0) 995 907

6922

Engr. Victor John Anunciado Instructor

Email: vjlanunciado@universityofbohol.edu.ph, Cell: 63 (0)

945 480 9029

SKILLS

C programming, C++ programming, C# programming,
Java Software Developer, AutoCAD 2D & 3D Designing,
Proteus 8 Professional PCB Development - Experienced

ONLINE PORTFOLIO

URL/Link: Portfolio (rumilchristiant-seloveres-dev-

portfolio.pages.dev)

CERTIFICATES/WORKSHOPS AND SEMINARS ATTENDED:

June 10, 2016	Community - Based Computer Literacy Course - TESDA
March 22, 2019	Computer Systems Servicing - NCII, TESDA
April 18, 2022	For Builders: Create Tomorrow - COMPESA Seminar
November 12, 2022	It Starts with Us: Challenge Yourself – COMPESA Seminar
December 01, 2022	Eagle CAD: PCB Design and Development – COMPESA
Seminar	
December 09, 2022	First COMFESTA 2022
January 2023	Emergency First Aid Training
May 20, 2023	Demystifying Innovation V1.0: Bridging the Gap Between
Ideas and Implementation	
June 22, 2023	National ICT Month ICT Learning and Certification Summit
•	on and Communication Technology Diliman Quezon City
September 16, 2023	MATLAB Onramp - MathWorks Training Services
September 2023	Seminar on PhilNITS Certification Exams
October 2-3, 2023	BHL i2i - Panda Tea Garden Suites, Tagbilaran City
October 13, 2023	Philippine Startup Challenge 8 – Top 25 Regional Pitching
Competition: Team CradleTalk – University of Bohol	
October 2023	Top 25 Regional Finalists in the 8th Annual Philippine
Startup Challenge - 18th F	
October 2023	Webinar on Quantum Computing Lecture Series and
Hackathon	
December 09, 2023	3D Printing Design - COMFESTA 2023
December 09, 2023	Sumobot Competition, 2 nd Runner Up – COMFESTA 2023
December 09, 2023	Sumobot Competition - COMFESTA 2023
February 02, 2024	Introduction to CISCO Networking Academy and Skills For
All Training	
February 02, 2024	Introduction to Cybersecurity course- CISCO
March 06, 2024	CrypTalk – Crypto & Web3 Education Caravan
March 14, 2024	Get Connected course – Cisco Networking Academy
March 15, 2024	Networking Basics course - CISCO
March 16, 2024	Cyber Threat Management course – CISCO
March 17, 2024	Computer Hardware Basic course – CISCO
April 11, 2024	Branding 101 and Adobe Illustrator training course
April 11, 2024	Design Sprint Workshop
April 11, 2024	Figma training course
April 11, 2024	IT Internship Program – 240 hrs
April 11, 2024	Laravel training course
April 11, 2024	In Preparation for Your Future: Portfolio Workshop -
COMPESA Seminar	
April 13, 2024	Enhancing Software Development Skillset - COMPESA
Seminar	
April 29, 2024	Digital Cites Program's IT-BMP Career Fair

I hereby certify that the above-mentioned information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.